Finding Aid for the Joseph Chouinard Papers, 1926-2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Concert programs, 1937-2007, IV.; Folder 109-232
  - Programs for performances including Joseph Chouinard 1948-2002, IV.A; Folder 109-145
    - 1981, 6 programs (Box 3, Folder 136)
      1981-03-29 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1981-04-12 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1981-04-17 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1981-05-17 Center for Human Development (Jersey City, N.J.)
      1981-06-07 Manhattan Plaza L.A.M.P. Concert
      1981-06-18 Erie Bayfront Orchestra
    - 1982-12-19, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 137)
      Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    - 1983, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 138)
      1983-12-18 Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      1983-12-25 Sacred Heart Church (Wimbledon, U.K.) Program: contains signatures of performers
    - 1984, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 139)
      1984-01-18 Royal Holloway College Chapel, Music List for Lent Term
      1984-03-20 Pro Musica Chorus of London Haydn's Creation and Mendelssohn's Elijah Includes newspaper clippings and a rehearsal schedule
    - 1987-12-02, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 140)
      State University of New York College at Fredonia
    - 1988, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 141)
      1988-02-11 State University of New York College at Fredonia, Orchesis
      1988-11-17 State University of New York College at Fredonia
    - 1989-11-09, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 142)
      State University of New York College at Fredonia La Boheme
    - 1990-09-08, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 143)
      State University of New York College at Fredonia, School of Music Second Annual Opera Fund Benefit Concert Includes newspaper clippings
    - 2002, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 144)
      2002-06-15 Allegheny Summer Music Festival
    - undated, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 145)
      Unitarian Universalist Church of Amherst (Williamsville, N.Y.)
      Shorter College (Rome, Ga.) The Christmas Story
  - Programs collected by Joseph Chouinard 1937-2007, IV.B; Folder 237
    Arranged in chronological order within folder.
    - Allegheny Summer Music Festival, 1979, 2003, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 146)
      1979 Season includes poster
      2003 Season
    - Amato Opera (New York, N.Y.), 1976-02-28, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 147)
      La Battaglia di Legnano
    - American Church in Paris, 1957, 1971, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 148)
      1957-09-22 Centennial program
      1971-09-26
    - American Guild of Organists, Greater Hartford Chapter, 1949-01-25, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - American Savoyards (New York, N.Y.), 1961-07-13, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 150)
      The Student Prince
    - Barclay (Chicago, Ill.), 1952-05-21, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 151)
      Fritz Krueger
    - Bargemusic (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1998-10-08, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 152)
      Signed by performers Mark Peskanov, Toby Hoffman and Fred Sherry
    - Beethoven Festival (Detroit, Mich.), 1977-11-02, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Berkshire Music Festival, 1950-1953, 3 programs (Box 3, Folder 154)
      1950-08-08
      1953 Season Includes list of music for choral conducting department as well as listing of students for the season including contact information
      1953 Season Small Choir
    - Bolshoi Ballet, 1963, 1975, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 155)
      1963-10-12
      1975-06-01
    - Bronx Arts Ensemble, 2002, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 156)
      Includes flyer with note from Kenneth Cooper and promotion for 2002-2003 season
    - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 1977, 2002, 3 programs (Box 3, Folder 157)
      1977-05-24
      2002-07-20
      2002-07-27
    - Bushnell Memorial Hall (Hartford, Conn.), 1943, 1950, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 158)
      circa 1943 Porgy and Bess
      190-04-23
    - Calvary Baptist Church (New York, N.Y.), 1953, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 159)
      1953-01-26
      1953-04-05
    - Chattanooga Symphony & Opera, circa November 1955, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 160)
      Newspaper clipping included
    - Chautauqua Opera Association, 2002-2003, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 161)
      2002-07-19 Macbeth
      2003-07-18 Romeo and Juliet
    - Chautauqua Symphony Orchestra, 1978-07-28, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Chicago Opera Association, circa January 1916, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Claremont College, 1970-1971, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 164)
      Season
    - Community Concerts, Inc., circa 1938-1971, 3 programs (Box 3, Folder 165)
      circa 1938
      1955-56 Season
      1970-71 Season
    - Concertgebouworkest (Amsterdam, Netherlands), 1957-11-27, 1 program (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Conservatoire américain de Fontainebleau, 1957-08, 2 programs (Box 3, Folder 167)
      1957-08-23
      1957-08-27
    - Eastman School of Music, 1969-07-28, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Eaton Auditorium, circa April 1937, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - English Chamber Orchestra, 1983, 1984, 2 programs (Box 4, Folder 170)
      1983-84 Season
      1984-05-14 Includes flyer
    - English National Opera, 1983, 1984, 3 programs (Box 4, Folder 171)
      1983-12-01 The Adventures of Mr. Broucik
      1983-12-23 Mireille
      1984-03-31 War and Peace
    - First Presbyterian Church (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1951-1952, 3 programs (Box 4, Folder 172)
      1951-09-26
      1951-09-30
      circa February 1952
    - Florida International Music Festival at Daytona Beach, 1967, 5 programs (Box 4, Folder 173)
      1967 Season
      1967 London Orchestra Program
      1967-07-16
      1967-07-24
    - Fredonia Suzuki Piano Institute, 1990-06-27, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Friends of Music of the Free Library of Philadelphia, 1969-1970, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Friends of the Music at St. Paul's (Buffalo, N.Y.), 2007-04-13, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Goldsmith's College (London, England), 1984-07-06, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 177)
      Contains list of contributors and a handlist for the exhibition
    - Grant Park Concerts, 1972, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Harpur College, 1961, undated, 2 programs (Box 4, Folder 179)
      1961-11-18
      undated Adele Addison S. Hurok Presents
    - Her Majesty's Theatre (Montréal, Québec), circa April 1962, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 180)
      The Sound of Music
    - Hopkins Center Summer Program (Dartmouth, N.H.), 1965, 2 programs (Box 4, Folder 181)
      1965-07-07
      1965-07-11
    - Imperial Theatre (Organization: New York, N.Y.), 2007-05-02, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 182)
      Coram Boy
    - Joseph Papp Public Theatre (Organization: New York, N.Y.), 2003-12, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 183)
      Caroline, or Change Includes xeroxed clipping from NY Times dated 2004/05/03
    - Juilliard School, 1975-1977, 2 programs (Box 4, Folder 184)
      1975-02-28
      1977-04-28
    - Julius Hartt School of Music, 1949-1951, 4 programs (Box 4, Folder 185)
      1949 Season
      1949-05-11
      1950 Season
      1951-01-26
    - Lemonade Opera, Presented by the Village Presbyterian Church, undated, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 186)
      Don Giovanni
    - Leningrad Philharmonic, 1973-11-22, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 2005-05-08, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 188)
      Great Performers Series
    - London Festival Ballet, 1983-12-27, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Longacre Theatre (Organization: New York, N.Y.), undated, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 190)
      The Belle of Amherst
    - L'Orangerie du Chateau de Sceaux, 1971-09-02, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Lyric Opera of Chicago, 1980-10-25, 1 program (Box 4, Folder 192)
      Atilla Includes note from Gilda Romo and her tour schedule for August-December, 1980
    - Manhattan School of Music (New York, N.Y.), 1988, 2001-2004, 3 programs (Box 5, Folder 193)
      1988-05-01
      2001-04-26
      2004-04-28
    - Mendelssohn Club of Philadelphia, 1953-12-29, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.), 1949-2004, 4 programs (Box 5, Folder 195)
      1949-03-12 Salome
      1976-12-15
      2004-12-29
      undated Zaza
    - Moscow Philharmonic Orchestra, undated, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Musical Arts Foundation (Binghamton, N. Y.), 1960-04-19, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 197)
      Contains correspondence to ‘Mom & Babe’
    - NBC Symphony Orchestra, 1949-03-12, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 1948-01-12, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - New York City Ballet, 2006-05-07, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 200)
      In Vento includes Playbill plus paper program
    - New York City Opera, 1951-1963, 3 programs (Box 5, Folder 201)
      1951 Season
      1960-03-22 The Ballad of Baby Doe
      1963-12-06 Don Giovanni performed at Cornell University
    - New York Philharmonic, 2003-11, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Oberlin Wind Ensemble, 2004-11-12, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Opéra de Paris, 1958-01-31, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 204)
      Dialogues des Carmélites
    - Opéra-Comique (Paris, France), 1971-09-04, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 205)
      Les noces de Figaro
    - Philadelphia Civic Grand Opera Company, 1952-02-21, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 206)
      1952-02-21 Amelia Goes to the Ball- I Pagliacci
    - Philadelphia Forum, 1951-10-26, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 207)
      Don Juan in Hell
    - Philadelphia Orchestra, 1963-1966, 2 program (Box 5, Folder 208)
      1963-1964 Season
      1965-1966 Season
    - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, 1990-12-06, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Riverside Church (New York, N.Y.), 1953-01-11, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Royal Holloway and New Bedford College, 1982-1984, 3 programs (Box 5, Folder 211)
      1982-11-23
      1983-11-22
    - Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, 1950, undated, 2 programs (Box 5, Folder 212)
      1950-12-08 performance held at Kleinhans Music Hall (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    - Sadler's Wells Royal Ballet, 1983-12-31, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 213)
      Coppelia
    - San Carlo Opera Company, undated, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - San Francisco Opera, 1972, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 215)
      Includes two promotional materials
    - San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, 1945, 5 programs (Box 5, Folder 216)
      1945-02-15
      1945-02-23
      1945-03-29
      1945-04-06
    - St. Bartholomew's Church (New York, N.Y.), 1960-2006, 3 programs (Box 5, Folder 217)
      1960-1961 Sunday Afternoon Season
      1976-07-19
      2006-05-07
      2006-09-17
    - St. James Theatre (Organization: New York, N.Y.), 1985-11-25, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 218)
      Jerry's Girls
    - St. Peter's Church (Staines, England), 1984, 2 programs (Box 5, Folder 219)
      1984-06-12
      1984-06-30 Includes information on Flower Festival and historical notes about the Church
    - St. Thomas' Church (New York, N.Y.), 1999-03-21, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 220)
      1999-03-21
    - State University of New York at Binghamton, 1966, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 221)
      Marilyn Horne
    - State University of New York at Buffalo, Center for the Arts, 2006-2007, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - State University of New York College at Fredonia, 1986, 1987, 2 programs (Box 5, Folder 223)
      1986-10-15
      1987-07-24
    - Teatro Instabile, 2000-05-07, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 224)
      La Griselda Includes 3 ticket stubs
    - Ti-Ahwaga Community Players (Oswego, N.Y.), 1963-01-12, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 225)
      Cosi fan tutte
    - Toronto Symphony, 1938-1939, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Trinity Church (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1980-05-11, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - University of Alabama String Quartet, 1955, undated, 2 programs (Box 5, Folder 228)
      1955-03-06
    - University of Connecticut Chorus, circa 1972-03, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 229)
      Handel's Israel in Egypt
    - Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.), 1944-04-23, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Widnes Arts Council (Widnes, England), 1962-04-14, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 231)
      Handel's Messiah
    - Windsor Festival, 1982, 1 program (Box 5, Folder 232)
- Publicity and promotional materials, 1951-2007, V.; Folder 233-237
  V.A Publicity and promotional material for music events
  V.B Publicity and promotional material for non-music events
  - Publicity and promotional material for music events 1951-2007, V.A; Folder 233-236
    - 1951-1967, 7 items (Box 6, Folder 233)
      1951-1952 season Philadelphia Civic Grand Opera Company
      1952-06-19 Tamiment Chamber Music Festival
      1957 souvenir program National Music Camp (Interlochen, MI.)
      1965-06-28 Hopkins Center, Dartmouth College: Contains flyer and brochure
      1967-06-14 Harpur College performance by the New York Woodwind Quintet
      1967-07-10 Teatro dei Differenti, A Summer School
    - 1971-1984, 8 items (Box 6, Folder 234)
      1971-1972 season American Berlioz Society
      1979-09-24 Metropolitan Opera Cruz-Romo, Gilda
      1979-11-14 92nd Street Y (New York, N.Y.) Kenneth Cooper
      1983-01-24 Wigmore Hall (London, England)
      circa August 1983 Victoria Palace (London, England) premier of Electric Ice
      circa September 1983 Victoria Palace (London, England) production of Electric Ice
      1983-10 Cathedral and Abbey of Saint Alban (England)
      1984-12-13 Mongiardo, Josephine: contains biographic handout
    - 2002-2007, 3 items (Box 6, Folder 235)
      circa October 2002 Berkshire Bach Society
      2004-04-17 Mannes College of Music, Faculty Recital
      2007-02-15 S.E.M. Ensemble (New York, N.Y.)
    - undated, 10 items (Box 6, Folder 236)
      Apollo Opera, Inc. (New York, N.Y.) production of Philemon et Baucis
      Calvary Episcopal Church (New York, N. Y.)
      Cleveland Orchestra
      Greater London Council performance of Sonant
      Moore, Kermit
      Royal Danish Ballet
      Swarthout, Gladys
      Theatre Royal, Drury Lane (London, England) performance of Pirates of Penzance
  - Publicity and promotional material for non-music events 1979-1999, V.B; Folder 237
    Arranged in alphabetical order by institution name within folder.
    - Publicity and promotional material for non-music events, 1979-1999, 8 items (Box 6, Folder 237)
      Bibliotheque Forney (Paris, France), undated
      Buffalo Garden Walk (Buffalo, N.Y.), 24 July 1999
      Centre Culturel Canadien Exposition Louise Forget undated, with note from Louise Forget, 9 April 1962
      Cortes, Nicholas art show, 16 September 1977
      Nashdom Abbey (Buckinghamshire, England), undated
      New York Shakespeare Festival Henry V, 1976 Season, featuring Meryl Streep
      La rue Molière, undated
      State University of New York at Buffalo, Edmund Hayes Society donor booklet, undated
- Press clippings, 1939-2008, VI.; Folder 238-309
  - 1939-09-06, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 238)
    Middletown (Conn.) Press
  - 1950-08, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 239)
    unidentified source
  - 1953-03-01, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 240)
    Diapason
  - 1954-11-11, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - 1955-04, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - 1955-05-16, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - 1955-06, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - 1955-07, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 245)
    1955-07-15 unidentified source
    1955-07-15 Middletown (Conn.) Press
    1955-07-28 Atlanta Journal
  - 1955-10, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 246)
    1955-10-28 Hamilton County Herald (Chattanooga, Tenn.)
    1955-10-30 Chattanooga Times
  - 1955-11, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 247)
    1955-11-02 Chattanooga Times
    1955-11-10 unidentified source
  - 1956-01, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 248)
    Chattanooga Times
  - 1956-03, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 249)
    1956-03-05 unidentified source
    1956-03-05 Chattanooga News-Free Press
    1956-03 unidentified source
  - 1957-03, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - 1957-04-02, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - 1957-06-28, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - 1957-11, 1 bulletin (Box 6, Folder 253)
    Fontainebleau Alumni Bulletin
  - 1958-04, 1 bulletin (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - 1958-11, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - 1959-03, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 256)
    1959-03 unidentified source
  - 1959-09-28, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 257)
    Binghamton Press
  - 1959-10, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 258)
    1959-10-11 Sunday Press (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    1959-10-11 Binghamton Sun
    1959-10-17 Sunday Press (Binghamton, N.Y.)
  - 1959-11, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 259)
    1959-11-06 unidentified source
    1959-11-30 Syracuse Herald-Journal
  - 1960-09-12, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - 1960-10, 4 clippings (Box 6, Folder 261)
    1960-10-01 unidentified source
    1960-10-15 unidentified source
    1960-10-15 Sun-Bulletin (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    1960-10-17 Sunday Press (Binghamton, N.Y.)
  - 1961-01, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 262)
    1961-01-21 unidentified source
    1961-01-30 Sun-Bulletin (Binghamton, N.Y.)
  - 1961-03-11, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - 1961-05, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 264)
    1961-05-09 Times (London, England)
    1961-05-20 unidentified source
    1961-05-28 Sunday News
  - 1961-07, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - 1961-08, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 266)
    1961-08-07 unidentified source
    1961-08-08 unidentified source
  - 1961-12-04, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 267)
    Elmira Star-Gazette
  - 1962-03, 7 clippings (Box 6, Folder 268)
    1962-03 Binghamton Press
    1962-03-06 Sun-Bulletin (Binghamton, N.Y.)
    1962-03-07 Binghamton Press
    1962-03 unidentified source
    1962-03-12 unidentified source
  - 1962-04, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 269)
    1962-04-15 New York times
    1962-04 Musical America
  - 1962-05, 6 clippings (Box 6, Folder 270)
    1962-05-20 New York herald tribune
    1962-05 unidentified source
    1962-05-26 unidentified source
    1962-05-27 New York times
    1962-05-28 unidentified source
  - 1962-07, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 271)
    1962-07 International Musician
  - 1962-08, 7 clippings (Box 6, Folder 272)
    1962-08 Rocky Mountain news
    1962-08 unidentified source
    1962-08-10 unidentified source
    1962-08-10 Aspen Times
    1962-08-29 Opera News
    1962-08 Musical courier
  - 1962-10, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 273)
    1962-10 Musical courier
    1962-10 Opera News
  - 1962-11, 1 bulletin (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - 1964-03, 4 clippings (Box 6, Folder 275)
    1964-03-13 Buffalo evening news
    1964-03-18 Buffalo evening news
    1964-03-18 unidentified source
    1964-03-19 unidentified source
  - 1964-12-17, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - 1964-01-11, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 277)
  - 1965-06-28, 1 newspaper (Box 6, Folder 278)
    Dartmouth Summer News
  - 1965-07, 3 newspapers; 4 clippings (Box 6, Folder 279)
    1965-07-03 Dartmouth Summer News
    1965-07-12 Dartmouth Summer News
    1965-07-14 Binghamton Press
    1965-07-15 Valley News (West Lebanon, N.H.)
    1965-07-25 Dartmouth Summer News
    1965-07 unidentified source
  - 1965-08, 1 newspaper; 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 280)
    1965-08-16 Dartmouth Summer News
    1965-08-23 Valley News (West Lebanon, N.H.)
  - 1966-12-11, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - 1967-01, 4 clippings (Box 6, Folder 282)
    1967-01-13 New York times
    1967-01-13 Columbia Daily Spectator (Organization)
    1967-01-14 Cue (New York, N.Y.)
    1967-01-18 Columbia Owl (New York, N.Y.)
  - 1967-07, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 283)
    1967-07-16 Daytona Beach Sunday News-Journal
    1967-07 unidentified source
    1967-10 unidentified source
  - 1969-01-22, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - 1969-02, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 285)
    1969-02-16 New York Times
    1969-02-20 Columbia Daily Spectator (Organization)
  - 1969-03, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 286)
    1969-03-05 Columbia Owl (New York, N.Y.)
    1969-03-05 Barnard Bulletin (New York, N.Y.)
  - 1969-04, 1 bulletin (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - 1972-02-01, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 288)
    San Bernardino Sun
  - 1974-04-29, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 289)
    Buffalo courier-express (Buffalo, N.Y.)
  - 1974-10-31, 1 newspaper (Box 6, Folder 290)
    U.B. Reporter (Buffalo, N.Y.)
  - 1974-11, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 291)
    1974-11-23 Buffalo courier-express (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    1974-11-23 Buffalo news (Buffalo, N.Y.)
  - 1975-03-10, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - 1975-04-20, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 293)
    Buffalo Courier-Express (Buffalo, N.Y.)
  - 1977-04-20, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 294)
  - 1979-08-17, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 295)
    Meadville Tribune
  - 1983-11-07, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 296)
    Dunkirk Observer: contains handwritten drafts of article
  - 1984-03-14, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 297)
    Dunkirk Evening Observer
  - 1985-01, 1 newsletter (Box 6, Folder 298)
    CIRCLings (Fredonia, N.Y.)
  - 1988-01-29, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - 1988-02-12, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 300)
    1988-02-12 Dunkirk Evening Observer
    1988-02 Leader (Fredonia, N.Y.)
  - 1988-11, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 301)
    1988-11-08 Dunkirk Evening Observer
    1988-11-15 Post-Journal (Jamestown, N.Y.)
  - 1989-11, 3 clippings (Box 6, Folder 302)
    1989-11 unknown
    1989-11-11 Dunkirk Evening Observer
    1989-11-13 Dunkirk Evening Observer
  - 1991-08-17, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 303)
    Dunkirk Observer
  - 1993-03-01, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 304)
    Buffalo News (Buffalo, N.Y.)
  - 1994-08-04, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - 2004-06-26, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 306)
    New York Times
  - 2006-04, 1 bulletin (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - 2008-01-26, 1 clipping (Box 6, Folder 308)
    Press & Sun Bulletin (Binghamton, N.Y.)
  - undated, 2 clippings (Box 6, Folder 309)
    unidentified sources
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Musicians--New York (State)--Buffalo; Chouinard, Joseph Jerod, 1926-2014
Genres
Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Concert programs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Joseph Chouinard Collection of Images
Mus. Arc. 71.2
Contains about 200 photographic prints, 19 slides, and 6 drawings collected by Joseph Chouinard. They provide documentation of his life and career, including his service spent in Okinawa towards the end of World War II.
Joseph Chouinard Collection of Scores
Mus. Arc. 71.3
Contains scores of 33 musical compositions written by Joseph Chouinard.